selector.com 2013-08-14

# Privacy – Selector

Architecture Media, which includes for the purpose of this document Architecture Media (Selector) and AGM Publishing, is committed to protecting your privacy in accordance with the relevant legislation being the Privacy Amendment (Private Sector) Act 2000 or equivalent legislation applying in New Zealand. This policy covers all personal information held by us.

You may be able to use our sites for a limited period without providing any personal details; however we may ask that you tell us some basic information about yourself. This statement explains our undertaking not to pass on any of your details without your prior knowledge and consent.

## Collecting information

We will ask you before collecting personal information and do so in a lawful and fair way. Generally, this information is requested to allow us to contact you, to facilitate your request to contact a company which has information listed on our sites, before you enter a contest or to order e-mail newsletters. For example: If you request further information about a product listed on our sites you will be asked for your address, telephone, facsimile and other contact details to facilitate this request.

We will tell you why we are collecting information and identify any third parties the information is disclosed to. We will tell you what impact it may have if you do not wish to provide the requested information. If we collect the information from a third party we will take reasonable steps to advise you of that collection.

We will provide details of how and where to contact us.

## Use of your personal details

Typically we will use your personal details for three primary purposes:

  * To make our websites easier for you to use without repeated log-ins.
  * To analyze areas of our sites to make improvements.
  * To report to the companies with information on our sites details about who is viewing their information.

## Access to your personal details

You can access your personal details on request except under circumstances where this access may be denied by provisions of relevant legislation.

## Updating your personal details

We will take reasonable steps to ensure that the information we collect, use and disclose is accurate, complete and up-to-date. Before allowing you to update your information we may require you to exactly match details as they appear in our records – details such as, First Name, Surname, Email Address, Suburb – to ensure that other people do not have access to your personal details stored by us.

## Security

Architecture Media will take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we collect is protected from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

## Cookies

To assist in your navigation of our sites and for our reporting functions Architecture Media websites may collect aggregated site-visitation statistics using cookies. If you choose to not have your browser accept cookies from us, you may not be able to view all information on our site.

## Disclosing information

We will only disclose personal information in accordance with the Act. This means if:

  * We told you when collecting it that it would be disclosed for that purpose or for a related purpose that you would reasonably expect;
  * We have your consent;
  * It is part of business assets which we are selling;
  * We are required by law to disclose it; or
  * It is otherwise permitted under the Act

## Opt out

Architecture Media will provide you with a low cost way to notify us if you wish to opt out from receiving further e-newsletters, marketing offers and the like. In accordance with the Act, any direct marketing offers will contain an opportunity to opt out.

## Our policy

This policy is available upon request. It may be reviewed and updated from time to time.

## Privacy enquiries

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, any privacy related dealings with us, enquiries concerning a possible breach of your privacy or you would like further information about our information management practices, you can contact the Associate Publisher, Audience Development and Events, Architecture Media, Level 6, 163 Eastern Road, South Melbourne, Victoria 3205 Australia Phone: +61 3 8699 1000 or the Publisher, AGM Publishing, 409 New North Road, Kingsland, Auckland 1149 New Zealand Phone: +64 9 846 4068.

#### Subscribe to our newsletter

Weekly update on new and interesting products.
